University Theses and Dissertations Collection UA098
Tufts Archival Research Center
- University Theses and Dissertations, 1894 -- 2013; 1995 -- 2013; UA098.002; 525.6 Linear Feet
  - Theses, 1450-1466, UA098.002.065 (Box 65)
  - Theses, 1467-1483, UA098.002.066 (Box 66)
  - Theses, 1484-1504, UA098.002.067 (Box 67)
  - Theses, 1505-1522, UA098.002.068 (Box 68)
  - Theses, 1523-1538, UA098.002.069 (Box 69)
  - Theses, 1539-1554, UA098.002.070 (Box 70)
  - Theses, 1555-1572, UA098.002.071 (Box 71)
  - Theses, 1573-1575, 1576 (Oversize), 1577-1591, UA098.002.072 (Box 72)
    Thesis 1576 is located in series 003, Oversize University Theses and Dissertations (UA098/003).
  - Theses, 1592-1616, UA098.002.073 (Box 73)
  - Theses, 1617-1639, UA098.002.074 (Box 74)
  - Theses, 1640-1660, UA098.002.075 (Box 75)
  - Theses, 1661-1678, UA098.002.076 (Box 76)
  - Theses, 1679-1692, UA098.002.077 (Box 77)
  - Theses, 1693-1705, UA098.002.078 (Box 78)
  - Theses, 1706-1717, UA098.002.079 (Box 79)
  - Theses, 1718-1731, UA098.002.080 (Box 80)
  - Theses, 1732-1741, UA098.002.081 (Box 81)
  - Theses, 1742-1761, UA098.002.082 (Box 82)
  - Theses, 1762-1780, UA098.002.083 (Box 83)
  - Theses, 1781-1795, UA098.002.084 (Box 84)
  - Theses, 1796-1815, UA098.002.085 (Box 85)
  - Theses, 1816-1829, UA098.002.086 (Box 86)
  - Theses, 1830-1851, UA098.002.087 (Box 87)
  - Theses, 1852-1872, UA098.002.088 (Box 88)
  - Theses, 1873-1894, UA098.002.089 (Box 89)
  - Theses, 1895-1916, UA098.002.090 (Box 90)
  - Theses, 1917-1937, UA098.002.091 (Box 91)
  - Theses, 1938-1956, UA098.002.092 (Box 92)
  - Theses, 1957-1965, UA098.002.093 (Box 93)
  - Theses, 1966-1975, UA098.002.094 (Box 94)
  - Theses, 1976-1983, UA098.002.095 (Box 95)
  - Theses, 1984-1995, UA098.002.096 (Box 96)
  - Theses, 1996-2007, UA098.002.097 (Box 97)
  - Theses, 2008-2025, UA098.002.098 (Box 98)
  - Theses, 2026-2043, UA098.002.099 (Box 99)
  - Theses, 2044-2061, UA098.002.100 (Box 100)
  - Theses, 2062-2070, UA098.002.101 (Box 101)
  - Theses, 2071-2081, UA098.002.102 (Box 102)
  - Theses, 2082-2096, UA098.002.103 (Box 103)
  - Theses, 2097-2112, UA098.002.104 (Box 104)
  - Theses, 2113-2131, UA098.002.105 (Box 105)
  - Theses, 2132 - 2146, UA098.002.106 (Box 106)
  - Theses, 2147-2162, UA098.002.107 (Box 107)
  - Theses, 2163-2181, UA098.002.108 (Box 108)
  - Theses, 2182-2193, UA098.002.109 (Box 109)
  - Theses, 2194-2200, UA098.002.110 (Box 110)
  - Theses, 2201-2208, UA098.002.111 (Box 111)
  - Theses, 2209-2217, UA098.002.112 (Box 112)
  - Theses, 2218-2229, UA098.002.113 (Box 113)
  - Theses, 2230-2246, UA098.002.114 (Box 114)
  - Theses, 2247-2260, UA098.002.115 (Box 115)
  - Theses, 2261-2278, UA098.002.116 (Box 116)
  - Theses, 2279-2299, UA098.002.117 (Box 117)
  - Theses, 2300-2315, UA098.002.118 (Box 118)
  - Theses, 2316-2328, UA098.002.119 (Box 119)
  - Theses, 2329-2340, UA098.002.120 (Box 120)
  - Theses, 2341-2358, UA098.002.121 (Box 121)
  - Theses, 2359-2373, UA098.002.122 (Box 122)
  - Theses, 2374-2382, UA098.002.123 (Box 123)
  - Theses, 2383-2391, UA098.002.124 (Box 124)
  - Theses, 2392-2401, UA098.002.125 (Box 125)
  - Theses, 2402-2419, UA098.002.126 (Box 126)
  - Theses, 2420-2429, UA098.002.127 (Box 127)
    Thesis 2426 consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 2430-2442, UA098.002.128 (Box 128)
  - Theses, 2443-2459, UA098.002.129 (Box 129)
  - Theses, 2460-2476, UA098.002.130 (Box 130)
  - Theses, 2477-2486, UA098.002.131 (Box 131)
    Thesis 2477 consists of three volumes.
  - Theses, 2487-2496, UA098.002.132 (Box 132)
  - Theses, 2497-2509, UA098.002.133 (Box 133)
  - Theses, 2510-2520, UA098.002.134 (Box 134)
  - Theses, 2521-2530, UA098.002.135 (Box 135)
  - Theses, 2531-2541, UA098.002.136 (Box 136)
  - Theses, 2542-2555, UA098.002.137 (Box 137)
  - Theses, 2556-2572, UA098.002.138 (Box 138)
  - Theses, 2573-2581, UA098.002.139 (Box 139)
    Thesis 2577 consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 2582-2590, UA098.002.140 (Box 140)
  - Theses, 2591-2600, UA098.002.141 (Box 141)
  - Theses, 2601-2615, UA098.002.142 (Box 142)
  - Theses, 2616-2631, UA098.002.143 (Box 143)
  - Theses, 2632-2648, UA098.002.144 (Box 144)
  - Theses, 2649-2659, UA098.002.145 (Box 145)
  - Theses, 2660-2674, UA098.002.146 (Box 146)
  - Theses, 2675-2688, 2689 (Oversize), 2690, UA098.002.147 (Box 147)
    Thesis 2689 is located in series 003, Oversize University Theses and Dissertations (UA098/003).
  - Theses, 2691-2698, UA098.002.148 (Box 148)
    Thesis 2693 consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 2699-2715, UA098.002.149 (Box 149)
  - Theses, 2716-2727, UA098.002.150 (Box 150)
  - Theses, 2728-2737, UA098.002.151 (Box 151)
    Thesis 2734 consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 2738-2749, UA098.002.152 (Box 152)
  - Theses, 2750-2762, UA098.002.153 (Box 153)
  - Theses, 2763-2776, 2777 (Oversize), 2778, UA098.002.154 (Box 154)
    Thesis 2777 is located in series 003, Oversize University Theses and Dissertations (UA098/003).
  - Theses, 2779-2792, UA098.002.155 (Box 155)
  - Theses, 2793-2807, UA098.002.156 (Box 156)
  - Theses, 2808-2826, UA098.002.157 (Box 157)
  - Theses, 2827-2835, UA098.002.158 (Box 158)
  - Theses, 2836-2850, UA098.002.159 (Box 159)
  - Theses, 2851- 2860, UA098.002.160 (Box 160)
  - Theses, 2861-2875, UA098.002.161 (Box 161)
  - Theses, 2876-2890, UA098.002.162 (Box 162)
  - Theses, 2891-2909, UA098.002.163 (Box 163)
  - Theses, 2910-2921, UA098.002.164 (Box 164)
  - Theses, 2922-2935, UA098.002.165 (Box 165)
  - Theses, 2936-2945, UA098.002.166 (Box 166)
  - Theses, 2946-2953, UA098.002.167 (Box 167)
  - Theses, 2954-2968, UA098.002.168 (Box 168)
  - Theses, 2969-2979, UA098.002.169 (Box 169)
  - Theses, 2980-2992, UA098.002.170 (Box 170)
  - Theses, 2993-3008, UA098.002.171 (Box 171)
  - Theses, 3009-3020, UA098.002.172 (Box 172)
  - Theses, 3021-3038, UA098.002.173 (Box 173)
  - Theses, 3039-3052, UA098.002.174 (Box 174)
  - Theses, 3053-3069, UA098.002.175 (Box 175)
  - Theses, 3070-3084, UA098.002.176 (Box 176)
  - Theses, 3085-3097, UA098.002.177 (Box 177)
  - Theses, 3098-3113, UA098.002.178 (Box 178)
  - Theses, 3114-3127, UA098.002.179 (Box 179)
  - Theses, 3128-3138, UA098.002.180 (Box 180)
  - Theses, 3139-3153, UA098.002.181 (Box 181)
  - Theses, 3154-3169, UA098.002.182 (Box 182)
  - Theses, 3170-3184, UA098.002.183 (Box 183)
  - Theses, 3185-3198, UA098.002.184 (Box 184)
  - Theses, 3199-3214, UA098.002.185 (Box 185)
  - Theses, 3215-3229, UA098.002.186 (Box 186)
  - Theses, 3230-3244, UA098.002.187 (Box 187)
  - Theses, 3245-3262, UA098.002.188 (Box 188)
  - Theses, 3263-3274, UA098.002.189 (Box 189)
  - Theses, 3275-3287, UA098.002.190 (Box 190)
  - Theses, 3288-3300, UA098.002.191 (Box 191)
  - Theses, 3301-3316, UA098.002.192 (Box 192)
  - Theses, 3317-3333, UA098.002.193 (Box 193)
  - Theses, 3334-3347, UA098.002.194 (Box 194)
  - Theses, 3348-3361, UA098.002.195 (Box 195)
  - Theses, 3362-3378, UA098.002.196 (Box 196)
  - Theses, 3379-3391, UA098.002.197 (Box 197)
  - Theses, 3392-3407, UA098.002.198 (Box 198)
  - Theses, 3408-3417, UA098.002.199 (Box 199)
  - Theses, 3418-3429, UA098.002.200 (Box 200)
  - Theses, 3430-3442, UA098.002.201 (Box 201)
    Thesis 3441 consists of three volumes.
  - Theses, 3443-3455, UA098.002.202 (Box 202)
  - Theses, 3456-3473, UA098.002.203 (Box 203)
  - Theses, 3474-3485, UA098.002.204 (Box 204)
  - Theses, 3486-3498, UA098.002.205 (Box 205)
  - Theses, 3499-3515, UA098.002.206 (Box 206)
  - Theses, 3516-3519, 3520 (Oversize), 3521-3529, UA098.002.207 (Box 207)
    Thesis 3520 is located in series 003, Oversize University Theses and Dissertations (UA098/003).
  - Theses, 3530-3541, UA098.002.208 (Box 208)
  - Theses, 3542-3555, UA098.002.209 (Box 209)
  - Theses, 3556-3571, UA098.002.210 (Box 210)
  - Theses, 3572-3586, UA098.002.211 (Box 211)
  - Theses, 3587-3602, UA098.002.212 (Box 212)
  - Theses, 3603-3616, UA098.002.213 (Box 213)
  - Theses, 3617-3620, 3621 (Oversize), 3622-3631, UA098.002.214 (Box 214)
    Thesis 3621 is located in series 003, Oversize University Theses and Dissertations (UA098/003).
  - Theses, 3632-3638, 3639 (Oversize) 3640-3644, UA098.002.215 (Box 215)
    Thesis 3633 consists of two volumes and is accompanied by a video cassette (VHS) and a sound cassette which are stored separately as folder 1 and 2 in box 39090014012799y. Thesis 3639 is located in series 003, Oversize University Theses and Dissertations (UA098/003).
  - Theses, 3645-3659, UA098.002.216 (Box 216)
  - Theses, 3660-3672, UA098.002.217 (Box 217)
  - Theses, 3673-3683, UA098.002.218 (Box 218)
    Thesis 3673 consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 3684-3695, UA098.002.219 (Box 219)
  - Theses, 3696-3711, UA098.002.220 (Box 220)
  - Theses, 3712-3727, UA098.002.221 (Box 221)
  - Theses, 3728-3743, UA098.002.222 (Box 222)
  - Theses, 3744-3756, UA098.002.223 (Box 223)
  - Theses, 3757-3768, UA098.002.224 (Box 224)
  - Theses, 3769-3786, UA098.002.225 (Box 225)
  - Theses, 3787-3804, UA098.002.226 (Box 226)
  - Theses, 3805-3818, UA098.002.227 (Box 227)
  - Theses, 3819-3828, UA098.002.228 (Box 228)
  - Theses, 3829-3834, 3835 (Oversize), 3836-3838, UA098.002.229 (Box 229)
    Thesis 3835 is located in series 003, Oversize University Theses and Dissertations (UA098/003).
  - Theses, 3839-3855, UA098.002.230 (Box 230)
  - Theses, 3856-3871, UA098.002.231 (Box 231)
  - Theses, 3872-3884, UA098.002.232 (Box 232)
  - Theses, 3885-3901, UA098.002.233 (Box 233)
  - Theses, 3902-3913, UA098.002.234 (Box 234)
  - Theses, 3914-3920, UA098.002.235 (Box 235)
    Thesis 3920 consists of three volumes.
  - Theses, 3921-3930, UA098.002.236 (Box 236)
  - Theses, 3931-3946, UA098.002.237 (Box 237)
  - Theses, 3947-3962, UA098.002.238 (Box 238)
  - Theses, 3963-3978, UA098.002.239 (Box 239)
  - Theses, 3979-3993, UA098.002.240 (Box 240)
  - Theses, 3994-4007, UA098.002.241 (Box 241)
  - Theses, 4008-4025, UA098.002.242 (Box 242)
  - Theses, 4026-4039, UA098.002.243 (Box 243)
  - Theses, 4040-4051, UA098.002.244 (Box 244)
  - Theses, 4052-4063, UA098.002.245 (Box 245)
    Thesis 4054 consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 4064-4076, UA098.002.246 (Box 246)
  - Theses, 4077-4089, UA098.002.247 (Box 247)
    Thesis 4083 consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 4090-4103, UA098.002.248 (Box 248)
  - Theses, 4104-4114, UA098.002.249 (Box 249)
  - Theses, 4115-4129, UA098.002.250 (Box 250)
  - Theses, 4130-4143, UA098.002.251 (Box 251)
  - Theses, 4144-4153, UA098.002.252 (Box 252)
  - Theses, 4154-4166, UA098.002.253 (Box 253)
  - Theses, 4167-4183, UA098.002.254 (Box 254)
  - Theses, 4184-4198, UA098.002.255 (Box 255)
  - Theses, 4199-4205, UA098.002.256 (Box 256)
    Thesis 4202 consists of three volumes.
  - Theses, 4206-4217, UA098.002.257 (Box 257)
  - Theses, 4218-4230, UA098.002.258 (Box 258)
  - Theses, 4231-4245, UA098.002.259 (Box 259)
  - Theses, 4246-4259, UA098.002.260 (Box 260)
  - Theses, 4260-4274, UA098.002.261 (Box 261)
  - Theses, 4275-4288, UA098.002.262 (Box 262)
  - Theses, 4289-4298, UA098.002.263 (Box 263)
  - Theses, 4299-4309, UA098.002.264 (Box 264)
  - Theses, 4310-4320, UA098.002.265 (Box 265)
  - Theses, 4321-4334, UA098.002.266 (Box 266)
  - Theses, 4335-4349, UA098.002.267 (Box 267)
  - Theses, 4350-4362, UA098.002.268 (Box 268)
  - Theses, 4363-4371, UA098.002.269 (Box 269)
  - Theses, 4372-4382, UA098.002.270 (Box 270)
  - Theses, 4383-4397, UA098.002.271 (Box 271)
  - Theses, 4398-4411, UA098.002.272 (Box 272)
  - Theses, 4412-4426, UA098.002.273 (Box 273)
  - Theses, 4427-4446, UA098.002.274 (Box 274)
  - Theses, 4447-4458, UA098.002.275 (Box 275)
    Thesis 4450 consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 4459-4473, UA098.002.276 (Box 276)
  - Theses, 4474-4486, UA098.002.277 (Box 277)
  - Theses, 4487-4503, UA098.002.278 (Box 278)
  - Theses, 4504-4520, UA098.002.279 (Box 279)
  - Theses, 4521-4533, UA098.002.280 (Box 280)
  - Theses, 4534-4544, UA098.002.281 (Box 281)
  - Theses, 4545-4556, UA098.002.282 (Box 282)
  - Theses, 4557-4570, UA098.002.283 (Box 283)
  - Theses, 4571-4582, UA098.002.284 (Box 284)
  - Theses, 4583-4595, UA098.002.285 (Box 285)
  - Theses, 4596-4610, UA098.002.286 (Box 286)
  - Theses, 4611-4623, UA098.002.287 (Box 287)
    Thesis 4613 consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 4624-4638, UA098.002.288 (Box 288)
  - Theses, 4639-4652, UA098.002.289 (Box 289)
  - Theses, 4653-4667, UA098.002.290 (Box 290)
  - Theses, 4668-4680, UA098.002.291 (Box 291)
  - Theses, 4681-4694, UA098.002.292 (Box 292)
  - Theses, 4695-4705, UA098.002.293 (Box 293)
  - Theses, 4706-4719, UA098.002.294 (Box 294)
  - Theses, 4720-4734, UA098.002.295 (Box 295)
  - Theses, 4735-4747, UA098.002.296 (Box 296)
  - Theses, 4748-4757, UA098.002.297 (Box 297)
  - Theses, 4758-4767, UA098.002.298 (Box 298)
  - Theses, 4768-4782, UA098.002.299 (Box 299)
  - Theses, 4783-4798, UA098.002.300 (Box 300)
  - Theses, 4799-4811, UA098.002.301 (Box 301)
  - Theses, 4812-4815, 4818-4826, UA098.002.302 (Box 302)
  - Theses, 4827-4841, UA098.002.303 (Box 303)
  - Theses, 4842-4859, UA098.002.304 (Box 304)
  - Theses, 4860-4875, UA098.002.305 (Box 305)
  - Theses, 4876-4892, UA098.002.306 (Box 306)
  - Theses, 4893-4903, UA098.002.307 (Box 307)
  - Theses, 4904-4916, UA098.002.308 (Box 308)
  - Theses, 4917-4932, UA098.002.309 (Box 309)
  - Theses, 4933-4947, UA098.002.310 (Box 310)
  - Theses, 4948-4961, UA098.002.311 (Box 311)
  - Theses, 4962-4973, UA098.002.312 (Box 312)
  - Theses, 4974-4983, UA098.002.313 (Box 313)
  - Theses, 4984-4997, UA098.002.314 (Box 314)
  - Theses, 4998-5008, UA098.002.315 (Box 315)
  - Theses, 5009-5025, UA098.002.316 (Box 316)
  - Theses, 5026-5042, UA098.002.317 (Box 317)
  - Theses, 5043-5060, UA098.002.318 (Box 318)
  - Theses, 5061-5073, UA098.002.319 (Box 319)
  - Theses, 5074-5085, UA098.002.320 (Box 320)
  - Theses, 5086-5099, UA098.002.321 (Box 321)
  - Theses, 5100-5114, UA098.002.322 (Box 322)
    Thesis 5110 by Eric A. Galm has an audio cassette.
  - Theses, 5115-5129, UA098.002.323 (Box 323)
  - Theses, 5130-5147, UA098.002.324 (Box 324)
  - Theses, 5148-5161, UA098.002.325 (Box 325)
  - Theses, 5162-5176, UA098.002.326 (Box 326)
  - Theses, 5177-5190, UA098.002.327 (Box 327)
  - Theses, 5191-5199, 5218-5219, 5227-5229, UA098.002.328 (Box 328)
    For 5200-5217 and 5220-5226, there are no hardcopies. They are available full-text.
  - Theses, 5230-5244, UA098.002.329 (Box 329)
  - Theses, 5245-5256, UA098.002.330 (Box 330)
  - Theses, 5257-5272, UA098.002.331 (Box 331)
  - Theses, 5273-5278, 5287-5296, UA098.002.332 (Box 332)
    For 5279-5286, there are no hardcopies. They are available full-text.
  - Theses, 5297-5314, UA098.002.333 (Box 333)
  - Theses, 5315-5330, UA098.002.334 (Box 334)
  - Theses, 5331-5337, 5351-5359, UA098.002.335 (Box 335)
    For 5338-5350 there are no hardcopies. They are available full-text.
  - Theses, 5360-5375, UA098.002.336 (Box 336)
  - Theses, 5376-5390, UA098.002.337 (Box 337)
  - Theses, 5391-5409, UA098.002.338 (Box 338)
  - Theses, 5410-5425, UA098.002.339 (Box 339)
  - Theses, 5426-5440, UA098.002.340 (Box 340)
  - Theses, 5441-5444,5450, 5463-5470, UA098.002.341 (Box 341)
    For 5445-5449 and 5451-5462, there are no hardcopies. They are available full-text.
  - Theses, 5471-5482, 5496-5499, UA098.002.342 (Box 342)
    For 5483-5495 there are no hardcopies. They are available full-text.
  - Theses, 5500-5517, UA098.002.343 (Box 343)
  - Theses, 5518-5535, UA098.002.344 (Box 344)
  - Theses, 5536-5551, UA098.002.345 (Box 345)
  - Theses, 5552-5564, 5574, UA098.002.346 (Box 346)
    For 5565-5573 there are no hardcopies. They are available full-text.
  - Theses, 5575-5589, UA098.002.347 (Box 347)
  - Theses, 5590-5607, UA098.002.348 (Box 348)
  - Theses, 5608-5610, 5626-5639, UA098.002.349 (Box 349)
    For 5611-5625, there are no hardcopies. They are available full-text.
  - Theses, 5640-5656, UA098.002.350 (Box 350)
  - Theses, 5657-5671, UA098.002.351 (Box 351)
  - Theses, 5672-5689, UA098.002.352 (Box 352)
  - Theses, 5690-5706, UA098.002.353 (Box 353)
  - Theses, 5707-5721, UA098.002.354 (Box 354)
  - Theses, 5722-5735, UA098.002.355 (Box 355)
  - Theses, 5736-5750, UA098.002.356 (Box 356)
  - Theses, 5751-5765, UA098.002.357 (Box 357)
  - Theses, 5766-5770, 5772, 5774-5779, UA098.002.358 (Box 358)
    For 5771, 5173, there are no hardcopies. They are available full-text.
  - Theses, 5780-5791,5793,5794,5796, UA098.002.359 (Box 359)
    ForTheses, 5780-5791,5793,5794,5796 there are no hardcopies. 57982 has CD attached. all are available full-text.
  - Theses, 5798, 5813, 5816, 5820-5829, UA098.002.360 (Box 360)
    For 5799-5812, 5814-5815, 5817-5819, there are no hardcopies. They are available full-text.
  - Theses, 5830-5838, 5841, 5843,5844, UA098.002.361 (Box 361)
    For 5830-5838, 55841, 5843,5844 there are no hardcopies. They are available full-text.
  - Theses, 5845-5863, UA098.002.362 (Box 362)
  - Theses, 5864-5880, UA098.002.363 (Box 363)
  - Theses, 5881-5894, UA098.002.364 (Box 364)
  - Theses, 5895-5896, 5898-5909, UA098.002.365 (Box 365)
  - Theses, 5910-5922, UA098.002.366 (Box 366)
  - Theses, 5923-5936, UA098.002.367 (Box 367)
  - Theses, 5937-5954, UA098.002.368 (Box 368)
  - Theses, 5955-5967, UA098.002.369 (Box 369)
  - Theses, 5968-5976, UA098.002.370 (Box 370)
  - Theses, 5977-5988, UA098.002.371 (Box 371)
  - Theses, 6000-6012, UA098.002.372a (Box data_value_missing_e4bbe47a3960ae1c1df030a82aa35a47)
  - Theses, 5989-5999, UA098.002.372b (Box data_value_missing_c81bb4c35c793d99339fd2ef518cf3e0)
  - Theses, 6013-6029, UA098.002.373 (Box 373)
  - Theses, 6030-6049, UA098.002.374 (Box 374)
  - Theses, 6050-6069, UA098.002.375 (Box 375)
  - Theses, 6070-6088, UA098.002.376 (Box 376)
  - Theses, 6089-6099, UA098.002.377 (Box 377)
  - Theses, 6100-6110, UA098.002.378 (Box 378)
  - Theses, 6111-6124, UA098.002.379 (Box 379)
  - Theses, 6125-6137, UA098.002.380 (Box 380)
  - Theses, 6138-6150, UA098.002.381 (Box 381)
  - Theses, 6151-6162, UA098.002.382 (Box 382)
  - Theses, 6163- 6175, UA098.002.383 (Box 383)
  - Theses, 6176-6192, UA098.002.384 (Box 384)
  - Theses, 6193- 6204, UA098.002.385 (Box 385)
  - Theses, 6205-6217, UA098.002.386 (Box 386)
  - Theses, 6218-6232, UA098.002.387 (Box 387)
  - Theses, 6233-6254, UA098.002.388 (Box 388)
  - Theses, 6255-6275, UA098.002.389 (Box 389)
  - Theses, 6276-6293, UA098.002.390 (Box 390)
  - Theses, 6294-6312, UA098.002.391 (Box 391)
  - Theses, 6313-6327, UA098.002.392 (Box 392)
  - Theses, 6328-6339, UA098.002.393 (Box 393)
  - Theses, 6340-6354, UA098.002.394 (Box 394)
  - Theses, 6355-6371, UA098.002.395 (Box 395)
  - Theses, 6372-6386, UA098.002.396 (Box 396)
  - Theses, 6387-6398, UA098.002.397 (Box 397)
  - Theses, 6399-6413, UA098.002.398 (Box 398)
  - Theses, 6414-6430, UA098.002.399 (Box 399)
  - Theses, 6431-6444, UA098.002.400 (Box 400)
  - Theses, 6445-6464, UA098.002.401 (Box 401)
  - Theses, 6465-6482, UA098.002.402 (Box 402)
  - Theses, 6483-6499, UA098.002.403 (Box 403)
  - Theses, 6500-6514, UA098.002.404 (Box 404)
  - Theses, 6515-6528, UA098.002.405 (Box 405)
  - Theses, 6529-6548, UA098.002.406 (Box 406)
  - Theses, 6549-6566, UA098.002.407 (Box 407)
  - Theses, 6567-6579, UA098.002.408 (Box 408)
  - Theses, 6580-6589, UA098.002.409 (Box 409)
  - Theses, 6590-6604, UA098.002.410 (Box 410)
  - Theses, 6605-6617, UA098.002.411 (Box 411)
  - Theses, 6618-6631, UA098.002.412 (Box 412)
  - Theses, 6632-6645, UA098.002.413 (Box 413)
  - Theses, 6646-6658, UA098.002.414 (Box 414)
  - Theses, 6659-6677, UA098.002.415 (Box 415)
  - Theses, 6678-6692, UA098.002.416 (Box 416)
  - Theses, 6693-6708, UA098.002.417 (Box 417)
  - Theses, 6709-6732, UA098.002.418 (Box 418)
    Missing 6724-6729 and 6731.
  - Theses, 6734-6746, UA098.002.419 (Box 419)
    Missing thesis 6733.
  - Theses, 6747-6762, UA098.002.420 (Box 420)
  - Theses, 6763-6780, UA098.002.421 (Box 421)
  - Theses, 6781-6798, UA098.002.422 (Box 422)
  - Theses, 6799-6814, UA098.002.423 (Box 423)
  - Theses, 6815-6830, UA098.002.424 (Box 424)
  - Theses, 6831-6847, UA098.002.425 (Box 425)
  - Theses, 6848-6879, UA098.002.426 (Box 426)
  - Theses, 6923-6933, UA098.002.427 (Box 427)
  - Theses, 6934-6947, UA098.002.428 (Box 428)
  - Theses, 6948-6977, UA098.002.429 (Box 429)
  - Theses, 6880-6895, UA098.002.430 (Box 430)
  - Theses, 6896-6922, UA098.002.431 (Box 431)
    The following ranges of theses are available through ProQuest Theses and Dissertation via the Tisch Library Catalog. DCA does not have physical copies of them: 6908-6912 and 6914-6919.
  - Theses, 7018-7034, UA098.002.432 (Box 432)
    The following range is not fully cataloged in the catalog. It is possible that these volumes are available from ProQuest Theses and Dissertations, but they are not represented locally as of 2010-07-01: 7013-7017.
  - Theses, 7015 and 7036-7043, 2006 -- 2008; UA098.002.433 (Box 433)
  - Theses, 6978-6992, UA098.002.434 (Box 434)
  - Theses, 6993 - 7012, UA098.002.435 (Box 435)
  - Theses, 5457, 5572, 5614, 5618, 5797, 5810, 6918, 6975, and unnumbered, 2008-08 -- 2012-08; UA098.002.436 (Box 436)
    - Point Vortices: Finding Periodic Orbits and their Topological Classification, 2012-08; UA098.002.436.00001 (Box 436)
    - Cold Atom Microchip Ringtrap Interferometry, 2009-05; UA098.002.436.00002 (Box 436)
    - Interactions of Adsorbates on Cu(100) Films Investigated by Surface Resistivity Measurements, 2008-08; UA098.002.436.00003 (Box 436)
  - Theses, 5201, 5208, 5339, 5340, 5350, 5454, and unnumbered, 1996 -- 1998; UA098.002.437 (Box 437)
    - Constraint-driven Global Routers, 1996-02; UA098.002.437.00001 (Box 437)
      by Wafa A. Al-Mansoori
    - Linear Control of an Active Magnetic Bearing Rotor System, 1998-05; UA098.002.437.00002 (Box 437)
      by John Anthony Bottari, Jr.
    - ICG Enhanced Contrast within Biological Systems for the Purpose of Diffuse Optical Tomography, 1998; UA098.002.437.00003 (Box 437)
      by Christopher Nunes
  - Theses, 5795, 5808, and unnumbered, 1995-02 -- 2013-05; UA098.002.438 (Box 438)
    - Digital Control of an Experimental Active Magnetic Bearing Rotor Using Open Source Software, 2007-05; UA098.002.438.00001 (Box 438)
      By Harland E.Alpaugh, Jr.
    - Estimation and System Modeling Using Information Theoretic Measures, 2007-05; UA098.002.438.00002 (Box 438)
      By Prabahan Basu
    - A Wavelet-based Technique for Differentiating White Gaussian Noise from Non-random Broadband Signals, 1995-05; UA098.002.438.00003 (Box 438)
      By Peter David Dolan II
    - Super-resolution Based on Iterative Deconvolution of Multiple Images, 2003-05; UA098.002.438.00004 (Box 438)
      By Farbod Khaghani
    - The Estimation of Transients in Noise Using the Wavelet Transform with Applications in Electrocardiograms, 1995-02; UA098.002.438.00005 (Box 438)
      By Henry Martin Polchlopek
    - The Effects of Magnetic Exposure on the Nervous System, 2013-05; UA098.002.438.00006 (Box 438)
      By George Saveriades
  - Theses 5177, 7044-7052, 1997 -- 2008; UA069.002.440 (Box 440)
- Oversize University Theses and Dissertations, 1932 -- 1988; UA098.003; 0.5 Linear Feet; 9 Volumes
  This series contains oversize University Theses from schools except Fletcher and Engineering.
  - Thesis 905, 1961; UA098.003.001 (Box 1)
  - Thesis 1576, 1969; UA098.003.002 (Box 2)
  - Thesis 2689, 1979; UA098.003.003 (Box 3)
  - Thesis 2777, 1980; UA098.003.004 (Box 4)
  - Thesis 3520, 1987; UA098.003.005 (Box 5)
  - Thesis 3621, 1987; UA098.003.006 (Box 6)
  - Thesis 3639, 1988; UA098.003.007 (Box 7)
  - Thesis 3835, 1988; UA098.003.008 (Box 8)
  - Thesis 179, 1932; UA098.003.009 (Box 9)
    Merritt, Warren Franklin. A study of the relocation and grade revision of the Santa Fe line between Temple and Brownwood, Texas. Tufts 1932. Contains a number of plans and blueprints.
  - Thesis 983, 1963; UA098.003.010 (Box 10)